as the world man had built was buried in ash a leader appeared a man who would later be known
as raffles the first raffles and his disciples embarked on a quest to find new light
and they did what raffles found was an unsullied flame the spark that would kindle an empire
here i come you ready you're no brother of mine
just give up i find you repugnant and it's hard to believe that you have memories of me
i have a few i remember that as a baby you used to laugh and cry you acted way more human
did the darkness scare you well it's all right now your big brother's got your back okay
what was that a memory of yours what a revolting image i said to get out of my head i need you
to see that we're brothers stop this no way i'm not stopping until i get the real you back
i'll go faster than light fly back to the time when we were a family and take hold of it
that shinra guy's a real devil he's so creepy yeah he is look at that grin where it is
he wore the same vicious smile the day his family was killed
are all of these shinra kusakabe's memories
just hold on he went past the speed of light backwards in time and linked me to his past experiences
honestly i don't know how i'll feel when i see you show it's been years but even now
i'm bound to you by the promise i made our mother you are family and i'll protect you
promises family bonds what meaning is there in such things
good question i do want to honor the promise i made to mom
but now that i've actually met you that isn't what's driving me anymore
your petty motives are of no interest to me
is that a fact
look kusakabe's here the mother killer yeah i heard he killed his baby brother too
really how he burned them up like the devil he is
it wasn't me when my home burned i saw the real culprit it looked like some kind of demon
i swear sooner or later i'm gonna find that thing and tear it a new one
did you see his face just now what a creep
ever since the fire my face tenses up into this grin when i'm nervous
they think i killed show
i am not some devil
wish i could see you again
mom show
why are you showing me these irrelevant memories
nothing you do will make us brothers again
i'm pretty sure that we're the same show
we were normal kids who grinned when we were happy
why can't we smile for real anymore
i don't have a past understand i have no need of one
this one feels different could it be a memory that i've lost
12 long years ago we were just an ordinary family you and me and mom
before the fire that tore us apart you and i could smile without even thinking about it
back in those days it was normal for us because we were happy back then
because we had each other and we had her
i love you and i love you and i love you and i love you both
is that our mother
hey what are you making us for dinner mama
some hamburgers
that sounds good
i'll be right there show let me wash my hands
don't worry i can help out leave it to me i'll calm him down
i'm on my way show
it's okay your big brother's here so don't be scared
i guess the wind must have blown it down
sorry buddy i'll get that off you real quick
dark
scared
alone
light
bet it was dark huh
well you're all right now show
your big brother came to save the day
hey now don't cry
you've got your own personal hero show
aww that make you feel better
whenever you need my help i'll come running
you were in the dark a long time
i didn't mean to leave you by yourself
i'm sorry
let me get you out of here okay
i'll take you someplace bright
you'll have nothing to fear
this is my
brother
come on
oh no what happened
listen this isn't your fault show
oh mea
hello hello
take what you got and leave now
you're wearing out your welcome
no one here wants to see you
hear you
think that you won from day one
but the devil will come
you know just why he wants you
don't you
go
He's screaming Meiji! Meiji! Meiji! Meiji!
I'll collect him and withdraw.
This is bad. Sheena is in no shape to keep fighting.
I don't believe I've met you before. But hey, let me guess.
Are you one of the people who stole Shil? If you find all the Adola Bursts, what will you do with them?
The Great Cataclysm from 250 years back didn't quite manage to burn everything.
If we collect enough Adola Bursts, then we can kick off a new Great Cataclysm and finish the job!
So toward that end, we're looking for Adola Burst wielders and using the bugs to make our own.
And we'll definitely need you in show!
Stop that! Why are you telling him all this?
Whoopsie doopsie! Who cares? It doesn't actually matter what he knows. He still won't be able to stop us.
But anywho, I think it's time I picked up our new prize.
Something on your mind, little buddy?
Before you take him, speak. What happened 12 years ago?
You wanna know? Well, between you and me, I'm a sucker for aggressive men.
So why didn't you force me to talk?
Stop screwing around.
Right! I'll get back to work.
Severed universe!
What's wrong? Nothing happened.
My power failed me. Have I been cut from grace?
Sho!
Hey.
What the... what have you done?
Wow, look at you. A sword in your chest? Get you this lively?
Okay, you're gonna come with me now, capiche?
Crap.
What the heck was that about?
Whoa!
She forced my blade away from her head somehow.
I... wasn't able to... save my brother.
I'm the one who's gonna put you down, understand, Devil?
So don't you die on me!
Oh, how's it going, gentlemen? No offense, but you weren't invited.
You... have to... be careful.
She has this weird move that lets her...
Just stop talking for now. We'll take care of it.
Now, you're kind of in my way, so go take a hike, bub.
Hmm?
No dice? That's weird.
What was that? Some kind of scare tactic? Come do your worst.
He has plasma.
That must be what was interfering with my electric signal.
How annoying! You're one pain-in-the-ass opponent, you know that!
Hurry, Hamea! We're running out of time! We need to leave soon!
Yeah, I'm aware, so shut your traps!
It won't even take me a second to crush these twerps!
How many of you are there?
My Tecchio!
It looks like their hardware fritzed out.
I'll keep her distracted! Help Shinra!
Sir!
Lieutenant!
Stupid jerk! So annoying!
Ugh, that plasma screws up my signal and keeps me from hitting their nervous systems!
There's so few people who can actually make plasma! Why'd he have to be one of them?!
Whoa!
Shinra, you're gonna be okay now.
Ah, an earthquake. Right on schedule, too.
Seems like a big one.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
That's because the evangelist is behind it!
Time's up, Hamea! Let's go!
See you later, if you survive!
No! They have show!
Dammit! Give my brother back to me!
Stop moving! They're losing blood!
We need to get out of here, too!
It's been ten minutes. Most quakes aren't nearly this long.
That woman said this was the work of the evangelist.
I don't get it. Why would they do this?
Sure. Where'd they take you?
Shinra! You need to focus on staying awake!
If you want to see your brother again, you've gotta survive!
To the emergency room?
Better idea. Let's call on our colleague.
When it comes to healing pyrokinetics, Director Huang has no match.
Director Huang! Director of Medicine Kaioko Huang!
We have an emergency!
What is it, Lieutenant Agu?
Hello, Captain Huang. Thanks for coming.
My crewman's badly hurt.
We received prior notice from Central.
I take it this happened in the Nether?
It did.
What exactly did you do in the Nether?
Do you know what's causing this incessant earthquake?
It almost looks like you broke some taboo down there and incurred the wrath of the Great Soul.
Long story short, we were hunting someone called the Evangelist who's built a cult, the Whiteclad.
They turn people into infernals. They're looking for people who have Adola bursts. The flames of the Underworld, Adola. They'll use those flames to torch the world.
We'll talk more once I've seen to your crewman.
Captain Huang.
You will be able to save him, won't you?
Possibly. Depends on how much strength he has left. I'm told that his heart, lungs, and spine were all damaged. Even if I can save his life, he may well end up paralyzed.
The patient's a third gen, right? And he has an Adola burst as well?
Correct.
I don't know if that's good or bad. This will be my first contact with the Sacred Flame. There's no telling what'll happen.
Our team would never be the same without him. So please, Captain. Do your best.
Do your best.
I'll try. I'll do everything I can.
I beseech thee, Sol. Please grant the light of life to Shinra.
We've successfully removed the sword. And his vitals are stable for now. All that's left is to treat him with my power. Not that it would be enough to heal a wound like this on its own. Honestly, his fate will rest on the strength of his flame.
No point waiting. The time has come! Stay back! Commencing final operation on Shinra Kusakabe! Rod of Asclepios!
Serpent! Revitalize him!
It's been an hour since the operation began.
Where are the others?
Sister Iris went off to pray for Kusakabe. Lieutenant Hinoa is being treated himself. And Leaked is following up on some leads.
But what about Vulcan?
He's with Lisa at the moment. We got her back, but she looks to be pretty traumatized.
What kind of fire company is this? It feels like a hospital.
You mean you don't know? Shouldn't surprise me.
First off, medical treatment is a sacred ritual that can only be performed by the Holy Soul Temple.
So since medical treatment is Company Six's specialty, they're an entity of the Holy Soul Temple, like the first.
I see now. So this building is like an ugly Holy Soul Temple, slash pseudo-hospital.
No, it's a fire force company. With treating the wounds of pyrokinetics, they say no one can hold a candle to Company Six's Captain Huang.
Apparently the reason for this is that she heals them with her own fire powers.
I didn't know flames could heal people. Does anyone know how that works?
Her fire takes the rod of Asclepios, the symbol of medicine. The serpent she makes can heal wounds, cure illnesses, you name it.
And when her patients have flames of their own, she can use that to relieve them of their suffering in an instant.
His flame is quite beautiful. At this rate, he should make a full recovery. That Adola burst is incredible.
But I had to use all his firepower to heal him, so he may not wake up for a few days.
I'm awake. Sky's clear. How long was I out?
What I wouldn't give for some rice. I feel like I'm about to starve.
What happened to Sho? I thought I'd saved him, but he must be back with the Evangelist by now.
It's a beautiful sky. I should be looking at it with my brother.
Damn.
You woke in only three days, as Captain Huang predicted.
It might just be the sunlight, but you don't even look all that pale.
That said, you're still on the mend. At ease, soldier. I'm glad you're feeling better.
With all due respect, sir, I'm lost. What are you doing here?
Checking up on you, of course.
But why would you? I'm just a random second-class fire soldier who's not in your company.
Have I put you out?
No, sir.
Then if you're feeling up to it, I think you and I should have a little chat.
About the fire that broke out 12 years back.
You get dressed first. Then we can take in some fresh air outside. I brought you some rice balls.
You always eat a lot?
Yeah, probably more than most.
You've certainly grown up.
So you are the fire soldier that I met 12 years ago.
And what's more, you saw what actually happened on that day.
Tell me, how much did you know?
Everything.
And had I reported the truth, you would have been spared a life of infamy.
No one would have thought you killed your family.
It doesn't matter what happened to me. What about my brother? Did you know that Sho was still alive or not?
Of course. I saw him.
Yeah. And did you know that he was kidnapped? Taken to be raised by the evangelist?
Yeah. I knew that too.
If you knew that, then why didn't you help him? Why didn't you say anything to me? If I had known, then I wouldn't have left Sho alone in that darkness for 12 whole years.
You had 12 years to grow up. 12 years to build your strength and still you nearly died. The truth would have done you no good.
That stab to the chest was a fluke. I'm stronger than I was when we sparred.
I doubt it. The fluke is that you survived. If you've truly gotten stronger, come and prove it.
you wanna crack you down. Yeah?
Have you beleza there?
You are still a few times.
I don't want help.
You are wow.
Take care.
We'll be right back.
Thank you.